quizData = [
	{
		"question":"Lean in: Women, work and the will to lead” is a book written by?",
		"questionOpt1":"Sandra Lerner",
		"questionOpt2":"Sheryl Sandberg",
		"questionOpt3":"Marrisa Mayor",
		"questionOpt4":"Meg Whitman",
		"rightAnswer":"Sheryl Sandberg",
	},
	{
		"question":"She was an analyst of Charles Babbage’s analytical engine and is considered by many the “first computer programmer. Who’s she?",
		"questionOpt1":"Ada Lovelace",
		"questionOpt2":"Grace Hopper",
		"questionOpt3":"Ursula Burns",
		"questionOpt4":"Sophie Wilson",
		"rightAnswer":"Ada Lovelace",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which women developed the algorithm behind the spanning tree protocol?",
		"questionOpt1":"Radia Perlman",
		"questionOpt2":"Tarah wheeler",
		"questionOpt3":"Marrisa Mayor",
		"questionOpt4":"Jean E. Sammet",
		"rightAnswer":"Radia Perlman",
	},
	{
		"question":"Ada Lovelace is celebrated as being the world’s first ever computer programmer. Which of these facts is not true about her?",
		"questionOpt1":"She is the daughter of poet Lord Byron",
		"questionOpt2":"She conceptualised a flying machine aged 12",
		"questionOpt3":"She was partially blind",
		"questionOpt4":"Her mentor was mathematician (and inventor of what would have been the world’s first computer) Charles Babbage
",
		"rightAnswer":"She was partially blind",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which of these tech giants does NOT currently have a female CEO?",
		"questionOpt1":"YouTube",
		"questionOpt2":"IBM",
		"questionOpt3":"HPE",
		"questionOpt4":"Trend Micro",
		"rightAnswer":"HPE",
	},
	{
		"question":"Of the 35 large resellers whose pay gap reports CRN examined, which had the lowest median pay gap, at 7.3 per cent?",
		"questionOpt1":"Softcat",
		"questionOpt2":"Daisy",
		"questionOpt3":"RM",
		"questionOpt4":"Computacenter",
		"rightAnswer":"RM",
	},
	{
		"question":"The median pay gap among UK firms in general stands at 9.7 per cent, according to the BBC. CRN conducted similar analysis of the pay gap reports of the 35 largest UK resellers. What was their average median pay gap?",
		"questionOpt1":"3%",
		"questionOpt2":"23%",
		"questionOpt3":"33%",
		"questionOpt4":"13%",
		"rightAnswer":"23%",
	},
	{
		"question":"Meg Whitman exited her job as CEO of HPE in January to join start-up NewTV. But which tech start-up did she take from $4m to $8bn revenues during her stint there between 1998 and 2008?",
		"questionOpt1":"Google",
		"questionOpt2":"Amazon",
		"questionOpt3":"Juniper Networks",
		"questionOpt4":"eBay",
		"rightAnswer":"eBay",
	},
	{
		"question":"Computer science pioneer Mary Kenneth Keller (who helped develop the basic programming language which would be brought to the masses via the ZX Spectrum in the 1980s) was also a:",
		"questionOpt1":"Nun",
		"questionOpt2":"Botanist",
		"questionOpt3":"Pianist",
		"questionOpt4":"Prominent Quaker",
		"rightAnswer":"Nun",
	},
	{
		"question":"How many of the world’s 206 technology billionaires are women, according to Forbes’ Rich List 2018?",
		"questionOpt1":"2",
		"questionOpt2":"5",
		"questionOpt3":"10",
		"questionOpt4":"15",
		"rightAnswer":"15",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which of these global reseller giants has a female CEO?",
		"questionOpt1":"SHI",
		"questionOpt2":"CDW",
		"questionOpt3":"Insight",
		"questionOpt4":"World Wide Technologies",
		"rightAnswer":"SHI",
	},
	{
		"question":"According to the Chartered Institute for IT, the percentage of UK IT workers that are female is:",
		"questionOpt1":"10",
		"questionOpt2":"17",
		"questionOpt3":"24",
		"questionOpt4":"31",
		"rightAnswer":"17",
	},
	{
		"question":"At 8.4%, which of these vendor giants reported the lowest (median) gender pay gap for its UK business in the run up to the 4 April reporting deadline?",
		"questionOpt1":"Microsoft",
		"questionOpt2":"Dell",
		"questionOpt3":"Oracle",
		"questionOpt4":"Cisco",
		"rightAnswer":"Microsoft",
	},
	{
		"question":"Lovelace’s ideas about computing were far ahead of her time. Roughly how long was it before the age of computer science dawned and technology is generally acknowledged to have caught up?",
		"questionOpt1":"20",
		"questionOpt2":"50",
		"questionOpt3":"100",
		"questionOpt4":"150",
		"rightAnswer":"100",
	},
	{
		"question":"Who is the world’s richest female tech tycoon, according to Forbes’ Rich List 2018?",
		"questionOpt1":"Denis Coates (founder of bet365)",
		"questionOpt2":"Zhou Qunfei (chairman of Lens Technology)",
		"questionOpt3":"Meg Whitman (NewTV)",
		"questionOpt4":"Eva Chen (CEO of Trend Micro)",
		"rightAnswer":"Zhou Qunfei (chairman of Lens Technology)",
	},
	{
		"question":"Which of these women led the team that created the first computer language compiler, which led to the popular COBOL language",
		"questionOpt1":"Grace Hopper",
		"questionOpt2":"Ada Lovelace",
		"questionOpt3":"Dorothy Hodgkin",
		"questionOpt4":"Adele Goldberg",
		"rightAnswer":"Grace Hopper",
	},
	


]

